"Kiss Or Kill"
(Episode 4)
A little bigger.
Slow down, slow down.
Get up, get up.
Get up.
Come on, be careful.
Be careful.
Second Uncle.
A-ren, take the kids downstairs.
Come on, follow me.
A-yan.
I heard something happened at your place.
I was worried sick.
But looking at it now,
it doesn't seem like a big deal.
Thanks to Nie Chuan.
He spotted the assassins
sneaking in just in time
and saved my life.
You mean the guide?
Yes.
He's the one who saved me.
You really trust him.
I only trust the facts.
There's a shipment coming
up in the next couple of days.
I need you to make the run.
Take him with you.
Got it, Second Uncle.
A-yan.
Thanks for your hard work.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Otherwise,
my brother and sister-in-law will blame me.
Go on.
Understood, Second Uncle.
Lin Yan.
What's up?
Do you really trust that guy so much?
When it comes to my business,
I make my own judgments.
What kind of judgment is that?
Are you really after his routes,
or are you after him?
He did save my life, after all.
In all these years, when have you ever
let an outsider into your home?
You even used yourself as bait to test him.
You did it on purpose.
Focus your smarts
on real business.
So I hit the nail on the head.
What's so special about this guy
that makes you
break all your old rules?
Do you really trust him that much?
You're overstepping your bounds.
Didn't you say
you hate leaving things to luck?
There's a first time for everything.
You're back.
You really made yourself at home.
A workspace with a pool.
Nice perks.
I'm very satisfied.
Put your clothes on.
What clothes?
First I got beaten up by your guys,
then I had to fight off
those amateur assassins.
Now,
I can only wait for you
to issue me a uniform.
Then I'll just wear whatever's available.
Your clothes fit me perfectly.
Stop staring.
Eat up while it's hot.
I made it for you.
You made this?
Who else?
Have you brought anyone else in here?
How is it? Not bad, right?
It's edible.
Edible?
Then don't eat it.
I actually took lessons.
You learned how to cook?
I picked it up from wilderness survival.
I couldn't just
eat survival rations for every meal.
The ingredients in your fridge
are really top-notch.
When I'm out in the wild,
I never get to eat stuff this good.
Clean yourself up in a bit.
You're coming with me.
Where to?
To work.
Nie Chuan.
It's pretty good.
What else do you want to eat?
You can order whatever you want.
Took you long enough.
What are you doing here?
Keeping an eye on you.
Second Uncle never trusts anyone.
We came all this way
just to pick up this little thing?
What do you know?
The buyer needs to
receive the sample first.
We only ship the goods
once they confirm it's all good.
And it takes two groups
to pick up a sample?
Quite the production.
Do you know what
dual-password verification is?
It's to prevent people like you.
People like me?
You're pretty cocky.
Hit me.
What are you looking at?
Don't think I won't beat you up.
You punk.
You drive, you pick the route.
Fine.
This buddy of yours
has no filter.
Get in.
You really treat me like a chauffeur.
You sit in the front.
It's cramped up front.
How is it cramped?
Isn't that how you got here?
I have long legs.
Do you know the rules?
Why so many rules?
What gives you the right
to sit next to my brother?
Get over here.
I don't think he minds.
Get in.
Did you hear? Get in.
Open the trunk.
Stop the car.
There's a checkpoint.
Under the seats,
check carefully.
I knew it wouldn't be this easy.
I've driven this road for over a decade,
and there's never been a checkpoint.
The day you show up,
Are you trying to say
I leaked the info?
You picked the route.
Am I supposed to be clairvoyant?
What do we do now?
We'll just have to ram through.
And then what?
What do you mean, 'then what'?
If you ram through and shots are fired,
we'll be completely surrounded.
What about the goods
in the car?
Then what do you suggest?
Look.
They're only checking plates and trunks.
Not the people.
Go on.
So we separate the car and the goods.
Lin Yan and I will take the
goods through the backroads.
You drive the empty
car and make a run for it.
Why should I be the decoy?
Because you know this road best.
And they definitely recognize this car.
You drive east,
and they'll most likely chase you.
Lin Yan and I
will take the goods and detour
through the west factory area.
We'll meet up at Hongling Road.
What if they don't chase me?
Even better.
Just drive straight to
Hongling Road and wait.
His plan works.
If I lure them away
and you get away with the goods,
who gets the credit?
You do, of course.
If the goods arrive, it's
because you lured them away.
If the goods are lost,
we all die together.
Fine. Let's do it.
If you try to screw me over,
I'll kill you.
Then you better pray nothing happens to me.
Gunshots.
Let's go provide backup.
Go.
Right up ahead.
Someone's coming.
Watch out!
You're hurt.
Cut the crap. Let's go.
Ouch!
I haven't even touched you yet.
I pulled something while running.
My arm almost snapped off.
Your arm's about to fall off.
Yet you still ran that fast.
Survival instinct.
If I didn't stick close to you,
what if you just left me behind?
Suck it up.
Wait a sec.
You're just pouring it straight on?
It's all we've got.
Go easy, then.
I really can't handle pain.
You're a grown man.
Afraid of a little pain?
I wouldn't dare cry about
it in front of anyone else.
Only with you.
The more you cooperate,
the less it'll hurt.
Hold still.
The more you cooperate,
the less it'll hurt.
Did you do that on purpose?
Yeah.
I can't believe you admitted it.
Move!
Hurry!
Not a bad wrap job.
Guess it doesn't hurt anymore.
I'm serious.
A little worse than mine,
but it's decent enough.
Don't flatter yourself.
Just complimenting you while I'm at it.
You were faking it.
Faking what?
Three years ago,
when you were getting stitches,
you didn't even blink.
Now, over a tiny scratch,
you're howling like you took a bullet.
You're as smart as ever.
Nie Chuan.
I...
You guys, search over there.
Got it.
Follow me.
Come with me.
Don't fall asleep.
It's not that cramped.
You don't need to be so close to me.
I'm just doing this for our safety.
Ouch.
I'm still injured.
They're here.
They shouldn't stick around for long.
Nobody here.
Look closer.
I thought I heard something.
If we get spotted,
I'll draw them away.
You grab the stuff and run.
No way.
Trust me.
I told you,
there's no way anyone could hide here.
It's clear. Let's go.
Let go.
We're safe now.
Shouldn't we do something?
Get out.
Let me see the wound.
It's fine.
It's just a scratch.
Is this the real you?
So, do you prefer
me faking the pain earlier,
or me right now?
Given the current situation,
we won't be able to leave
anytime soon.
Luckily, they just searched this area.
We should be safe for now.
Then let's
rest up right here.
Alright.
Let's set up camp here.
Then the task of gathering firewood
is all yours.
Me?
We can't leave tonight anyway,
so we might as well get some rest.
Overthinking won't help.
What's wrong?
Are you still thinking about someone else?
Black Scorpion can handle it.
I trust him.
He said you trust me.
You say you trust him.
So who do you actually trust more?
I suggest you talk less
and save your energy.
Going to the bathroom? Let's go together.
Pack up. It's time to go.
So soon?
It's almost dawn.
Feels like I slept for less than an hour.
Don't you know
what it means to sleep with one eye open?
I really don't.
Why don't you teach me?
Who's there?
Stop hiding.
I can already see you.
Whose kid is this?
I... I don't mean any harm.
I'm just so hungry.
Here.